{
  "mediumlevelquestions": [
    {
      "question": "What is 18 - 9?",
      "answer1": "8",
      "answer2": "9",
      "correct": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 21 - 13?",
      "answer1": "7",
      "answer2": "8",
      "correct": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 30 - 17?",
      "answer1": "12",
      "answer2": "13",
      "correct": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 25 - 14?",
      "answer1": "10",
      "answer2": "11",
      "correct": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 32 - 19?",
      "answer1": "12",
      "answer2": "13",
      "correct": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 40 - 22?",
      "answer1": "16",
      "answer2": "18",
      "correct": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 27 - 15?",
      "answer1": "11",
      "answer2": "12",
      "correct": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 35 - 20?",
      "answer1": "14",
      "answer2": "15",
      "correct": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 29 - 11?",
      "answer1": "17",
      "answer2": "18",
      "correct": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 24 - 16?",
      "answer1": "7",
      "answer2": "8",
      "correct": "8"
    }
  ]
}
